http://www.schwartzreport.net/privacy-policy

IF YOU ENJOY SR AND FIND IT USEFUL WOULD YOU PLEASE DONATE
When I began Schwartzreport my purpose was to produce an entirely fact-based daily publication in favor of the earth, the inter-connectedness and interdependence of all life, democracy, equality for all, liberty, and things that are life-affirming. Also, to warn my readers about actions, events, and trends that threaten those values. Our country now stands at a crossroads, indeed, the world stands at a crossroads where those values are very much at risk and it is up to each of us who care about wellbeing to do what we can to defend those principles. I want to thank all of you who have contributed to SR, particularly those of you who have scheduled an ongoing monthly contribution. It makes a big difference and is much appreciated. It is one thing to put in the hours each day and to do the work for free, but another to have to cover the rising out-of-pocket costs. For those of you who haven’t done so, but read SR regularly, I ask that you consider supporting it.
-- S
Yes, I support SR
Click on a Book Cover to Order
Privacy Policy
Who we are
Our website address is: https://www.schwartzreport.net.
Consent
By accessing this website, you accept our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use, and you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. In addition, by using our Service, or services across partnered and unaffiliated sites, you are accepting the policies and practices described in this Privacy Policy. Each time you visit our website or use the Service, and any time you voluntarily provide us with information, you agree that you are consenting to our collection, use, and disclosure of the information that you provide, and you are consenting to receive emails or otherwise be contacted, as described in this Privacy Policy. Whether or not you register or create any kind of account with us, this Privacy Policy applies to all users of the website and the Service.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
We may collect both “Non-Personal Information” and “Personal Information” about you. “Non-Personal Information” includes information that cannot be used to personally identify you, such as anonymous usage data, general demographic information we may collect, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, preferences you submit and preferences that are generated based on the data you submit and number of clicks. “Personal Information” includes information that can be used to personally identify you, such as your name, address and email address.
In addition, we may also track information provided to us by your browser or by our mobile application when you view or use the Service, such as the website you came from (known as the “referring URL”), the type of browser you use, the device from which you connected to the Service, the time and date of access, and other information that does not personally identify you.  We use this information for, among other things, the operation of the Service, to maintain the quality of the Service, to provide general statistics regarding use of the Service and for other business purposes. We track this information using cookies, or small text files which include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to a user’s browser from our servers and are stored on the user’s computer hard drive. Sending a cookie to a user’s browser enables us to collect Non-Personal Information about that user and keep a record of the user’s preferences when utilizing our services, both on an individual and aggregate basis.  The Company may use both persistent and session cookies; persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your session and until you delete them, while session cookies expire when you close your browser. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Service may not work properly.
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
If you use our contact form, we collect your name, email, and IP addresses.  Contact form submissions are kept for a period of 2 years for customer service purposes and are then deleted from the server. The information you share on a contact form is not used for marketing purposes.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “Cookies”, text files that are stored on your computer and enable analysis of your use of the website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is usually transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there. By order of the operator of the website, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, compile reports on website activity, and provide other services regarding website and internet use to the website operator.
The IP address transmitted by your browser as part of the Google Analytics will not be merged with other data from Google.
You may block cookies from being stored by adjusting the settings in your browser software; however, we would like to point out that in this case, you may not be able to use all of the features on this website to their full extent.
You can also block the collection of the data generated by the cookie and the data related to your use of the website (incl. your IP address) to Google as well as the processing of this data by Google, by downloading and installing a browser plugin available from the following link: http://www.google.com/settings/ads.
Who we share your data with
If you sign up for our mailing list your data is shared with our email list service, Mailchimp, which is used to send out our e-newsletters.
Personal Information:
In general, we do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise share your Personal Information with third parties without your consent. We may share your Personal Information with vendors and other third-party providers who are performing services for us. In general, the vendors and third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide for us.  For example, when you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, place an order, arrange for a delivery, or return a purchase, you consent to our collecting and using such personal information for that specific purpose, including by transmitting such information to our vendors (and their service providers) performing these services for the us.
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment processors, have their own privacy policies in respect of the information that we are required to provide to them in order to use their services.  For these third-party service providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so that you can understand the manner in which your Personal Information will be handled by such providers.
In addition, we may disclose your Personal Information if required to do so by law or if you violate our Terms of Use.
Non-Personal Information:
In general, we use Non-Personal Information to help us improve the Service and customize the user experience. We also aggregate Non-Personal Information in order to track trends and analyze use patterns of the Service. This Privacy Policy does not limit in any way our use or disclosure of Non-Personal Information and we reserve the right to use and disclose such Non-Personal Information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties at our sole discretion.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Site, or wish to withdraw your consent for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your Personal Information, please contact us by sending an email to webmaster@schwartzreport.net.
Additional information
How we protect your data
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page. Payment and credit card data is collected an processed through PayPal’s secure services and is covered by their privacy and security policies. Your credit card information is never revealed directly to us.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Our Commitment to Security
We have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures intended to protect your data. Of course, we cannot guarantee that your communications with the Services will never be unlawfully intercepted or that your personal data will never be unlawfully accessed by third parties. Any transmission of information is at your own risk
Age of Consent
By using the Service, you represent that you are at least 18 years of age.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy as business needs require. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here prior to the time they take effect.
Last Updated: May 21, 2018
Receive the Daily Schwartz ReportSubscribeStephan's Curriculum VitaeOpening to the Infinite
https://youtu.be/5GXevKr_PWE21st Century Radio Interview with Stephan
https://s3.amazonaws.com/nemopublicstreams/02_12_17StephanSchwartz_21stCenturyRadio.mp3https://youtu.be/aknh_O4Pj0c
Talking Social Change
Compassionate and life-affirming changes have the most enduring impact in our society. Author Stephen A. Schwartz and Social Activist Rick Ingrasci discuss social change, current challenges, and the ways we deal with them.Stephan A. Schwartz | Nonlocal Consciousness & the Anthropology of Religions and Spiritual Practiceshttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r4xxse7276U“The Hidden Path to Creativity” | Stephan Schwartz | TEDxOrcasIslandhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_K4YcaU5uqU&_=28 Laws of Change | Stephan A Schwartz | TEDxVailhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uHnqvhWQMV0&_=3
Follow me on Academia.eduArchives Archives
Select Month
December 2020  (40)
November 2020  (113)
October 2020  (126)
September 2020  (115)
August 2020  (128)
July 2020  (125)
June 2020  (124)
May 2020  (131)
April 2020  (125)
March 2020  (144)
February 2020  (120)
January 2020  (126)
December 2019  (122)
November 2019  (125)
October 2019  (124)
September 2019  (120)
August 2019  (130)
July 2019  (125)
June 2019  (118)
May 2019  (126)
April 2019  (121)
March 2019  (124)
February 2019  (117)
January 2019  (126)
December 2018  (127)
November 2018  (122)
October 2018  (122)
September 2018  (121)
August 2018  (125)
July 2018  (123)
June 2018  (121)
May 2018  (123)
April 2018  (117)
March 2018  (124)
February 2018  (113)
January 2018  (128)
December 2017  (127)
November 2017  (116)
October 2017  (81)
September 2017  (117)
August 2017  (122)
July 2017  (124)
June 2017  (117)
May 2017  (124)
April 2017  (121)
March 2017  (128)
February 2017  (107)
January 2017  (123)
December 2016  (118)
November 2016  (126)
October 2016  (122)
September 2016  (117)
August 2016  (77)
July 2016  (111)
June 2016  (120)
May 2016  (126)
April 2016  (121)
March 2016  (125)
February 2016  (114)
January 2016  (124)
December 2015  (110)
November 2015  (102)
October 2015  (125)
September 2015  (116)
August 2015  (121)
July 2015  (116)
June 2015  (112)
May 2015  (124)
April 2015  (121)
March 2015  (120)
February 2015  (116)
January 2015  (122)
December 2014  (119)
November 2014  (128)
October 2014  (129)
September 2014  (139)
August 2014  (135)
July 2014  (94)
June 2014  (140)
May 2014  (148)
April 2014  (118)
March 2014  (152)
February 2014  (132)
January 2014  (115)
December 2013  (149)
November 2013  (144)
October 2013  (154)
September 2013  (143)
August 2013  (137)
July 2013  (135)
June 2013  (135)
May 2013  (158)
April 2013  (128)
March 2013  (130)
February 2013  (133)
January 2013  (142)
December 2012  (134)
November 2012  (127)
October 2012  (114)
September 2012  (124)
August 2012  (144)
July 2012  (130)
June 2012  (87)
May 2012  (137)
April 2012  (134)
March 2012  (135)
February 2012  (123)
January 2012  (144)
December 2011  (134)
November 2011  (131)
October 2011  (124)
September 2011  (136)
August 2011  (128)
July 2011  (107)
June 2011  (108)
May 2011  (127)
April 2011  (132)
March 2011  (112)
February 2011  (117)
January 2011  (125)
December 2010  (133)
November 2010  (129)
October 2010  (124)
September 2010  (124)
August 2010  (101)
July 2010  (72)
June 2010  (104)
May 2010  (119)
April 2010  (102)
March 2010  (126)
February 2010  (113)
January 2010  (113)
December 2009  (124)
November 2009  (123)
October 2009  (117)
September 2009  (113)
August 2009  (119)
July 2009  (102)
June 2009  (116)
May 2009  (119)
April 2009  (101)
March 2009  (127)
February 2009  (108)
January 2009  (118)
December 2008  (119)
November 2008  (113)
October 2008  (119)
September 2008  (115)
August 2008  (109)
July 2008  (69)
June 2008  (115)
May 2008  (108)
April 2008  (111)
March 2008  (122)
February 2008  (106)
January 2008  (111)
December 2007  (100)
November 2007  (113)
October 2007  (106)
September 2007  (111)
August 2007  (103)
July 2007  (103)
June 2007  (119)
May 2007  (120)
April 2007  (109)
March 2007  (120)
February 2007  (98)
January 2007  (112)
December 2006  (100)
November 2006  (110)
October 2006  (119)
September 2006  (107)
August 2006  (109)
July 2006  (103)
June 2006  (101)
May 2006  (99)
April 2006  (114)
March 2006  (117)
February 2006  (106)
January 2006  (91)
Website Designed and Maintained by:
BethAlexander.com
